<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Argentina football team &#8211; Staging Stetson</title>
	<atom:link href="https://staging.stetson.com/tag/argentina-football-team/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://staging.stetson.com</link>
	<description>Welcome And Give Thanks</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Messi will play with our backs?&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/messi-will-play-with-our-backs/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/messi-will-play-with-our-backs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina football team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.stetson.com/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Argentina will play a friendly match with Australia in Beijing. Chinese football fans were happy that they will have the opportunity to see the football [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Argentina will play a friendly match with Australia in Beijing. Chinese football fans were happy that they will have the opportunity to see the football style of the captain of the World Cup winning team directly in the gallery. But after knowing the cost of watching Messi&#8217;s game live, their joy is gone.</p>



<p>On June 15, the Argentina-Australia match will be held at the 68,000-seat Workers Stadium. The minimum ticket price for the match is 580 yuan or $82. And the highest ticket price is 4800 yuan. The organizers said that the tickets will go on sale on June 5 and 8.</p>



<p>The Chinese are all over the social media about this high ticket price. Many people are talking about it on Weibo, the country&#8217;s social media. One Weibo user wrote, &#8216;I will report you (the host) for robbery.&#8217; Another said, &#8216;Will Messi play on our backs for 4800 yuan?&#8217;</p>



<p>Chinese football fans are dissatisfied with ticket prices. But the demand for tickets is not low. However, the authorities are taking strict steps to prevent tickets from being sold in the black market. It is said that visitors must enter the field by showing their identity cards. But even in this, ticket sales have started in the black market. Taobao, the country&#8217;s selling platform, has started offering various offers for ticket bookings. A seller asked 18,000 yuan for a VIP ticket.</p>



<p>Argentina&#8217;s match with Australia can be said to be a replay of the last sixteen match of the World Cup in Qatar. Messi-Martinez&#8217;s Argentina reached the quarter-finals after beating Australia 2-1 in the last sixteen of the World Cup in Qatar.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/messi-will-play-with-our-backs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
