<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>an accident &#8211; Staging Stetson</title>
	<atom:link href="https://staging.stetson.com/tag/an-accident/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://staging.stetson.com</link>
	<description>Welcome And Give Thanks</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:11:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Over 200 injured in train accident from Kolkata to Chennai</title>
		<link>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/over-200-injured-in-train-accident-from-kolkata-to-chennai/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/over-200-injured-in-train-accident-from-kolkata-to-chennai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[an accident]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[train accident]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.stetson.com/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coromandel Express train from Kolkata to Chennai in India suffered a terrible accident. The accident took place in Balasore, Odisha state, 250 km south of [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coromandel Express train from Kolkata to Chennai in India suffered a terrible accident. The accident took place in Balasore, Odisha state, 250 km south of Kolkata, around 7:30 pm today. Although more than two hundred people were injured, it is not known whether anyone died or not.</p>



<p>Odisha Chief Secretary Pradeep Jena told reporters at around 9:30 pm that the collision took place between the Coromandel Express, a local train and a freight train. Several coaches were derailed and many were damaged. About 60 ambulances and more than 15 units of the fire brigade were dispatched to the scene.</p>



<p>West Bengal Chief Minister Mamata Banerjee said that several people from Kolkata are in danger of being on this train and there is a danger of being injured. The Coromandel Express train was traveling from Kolkata&#8217;s Shalimar station to Chennai, the capital of Tamil Nadu in South India. Many people from Kolkata go to Chennai for treatment by this train.</p>



<p>Mamata Banerjee said that a team of 5 or 6 people is being sent to Odisha from West Bengal. He announced two emergency numbers for inquiries saying he was in touch with the Odisha government. These two numbers are 0091-33-22143526 and 0091-33-22535185.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/over-200-injured-in-train-accident-from-kolkata-to-chennai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
