<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Staging Stetson</title>
	<atom:link href="https://staging.stetson.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://staging.stetson.com</link>
	<description>Welcome And Give Thanks</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Messi will play with our backs?&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/messi-will-play-with-our-backs/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/messi-will-play-with-our-backs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina football team]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.stetson.com/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Argentina will play a friendly match with Australia in Beijing. Chinese football fans were happy that they will have the opportunity to see the football [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Argentina will play a friendly match with Australia in Beijing. Chinese football fans were happy that they will have the opportunity to see the football style of the captain of the World Cup winning team directly in the gallery. But after knowing the cost of watching Messi&#8217;s game live, their joy is gone.</p>



<p>On June 15, the Argentina-Australia match will be held at the 68,000-seat Workers Stadium. The minimum ticket price for the match is 580 yuan or $82. And the highest ticket price is 4800 yuan. The organizers said that the tickets will go on sale on June 5 and 8.</p>



<p>The Chinese are all over the social media about this high ticket price. Many people are talking about it on Weibo, the country&#8217;s social media. One Weibo user wrote, &#8216;I will report you (the host) for robbery.&#8217; Another said, &#8216;Will Messi play on our backs for 4800 yuan?&#8217;</p>



<p>Chinese football fans are dissatisfied with ticket prices. But the demand for tickets is not low. However, the authorities are taking strict steps to prevent tickets from being sold in the black market. It is said that visitors must enter the field by showing their identity cards. But even in this, ticket sales have started in the black market. Taobao, the country&#8217;s selling platform, has started offering various offers for ticket bookings. A seller asked 18,000 yuan for a VIP ticket.</p>



<p>Argentina&#8217;s match with Australia can be said to be a replay of the last sixteen match of the World Cup in Qatar. Messi-Martinez&#8217;s Argentina reached the quarter-finals after beating Australia 2-1 in the last sixteen of the World Cup in Qatar.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/messi-will-play-with-our-backs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Food prices hit 2-year low in May: FAO</title>
		<link>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/food-prices-hit-2-year-low-in-may-fao/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/food-prices-hit-2-year-low-in-may-fao/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[commodity price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[foodstuff]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Nations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.stetson.com/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.N. Food Organization&#8217;s global food price index fell to a two-year low in May. Because, despite the increase in the price of sugar and [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.N. Food Organization&#8217;s global food price index fell to a two-year low in May. Because, despite the increase in the price of sugar and meat, the prices of vegetable oil, food grains and dairy products have decreased relatively more, and the overall price index is downward.</p>



<p>The Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (FAO) monitors price fluctuations of the most traded commodity globally. The average food price index in May was 124.3 points compared to last month&#8217;s revised 127.7 points. The index for April was said to be 127.2.</p>



<p>The score was lowest in May compared to April 2021. That means it&#8217;s now down 22 percent from its all-time high point reached in March 2022 after Russia&#8217;s attack on Ukraine. The global organization has been publishing this index since 1990.</p>



<p>FAO&#8217;s cereal price index fell by about 5 percent in May from the previous month. Prices were influenced by the prospect of ample supply and the extension of the Black Sea grain contract, opening up opportunities for exports from Ukraine.</p>



<p>But international rice prices continued to rise in May as some exporting countries tightened supplies, FAO said. The company last month expressed concern over the price hike of this staple product.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/food-prices-hit-2-year-low-in-may-fao/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 200 injured in train accident from Kolkata to Chennai</title>
		<link>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/over-200-injured-in-train-accident-from-kolkata-to-chennai/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/over-200-injured-in-train-accident-from-kolkata-to-chennai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[an accident]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[train accident]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.stetson.com/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coromandel Express train from Kolkata to Chennai in India suffered a terrible accident. The accident took place in Balasore, Odisha state, 250 km south of [&#8230;]</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coromandel Express train from Kolkata to Chennai in India suffered a terrible accident. The accident took place in Balasore, Odisha state, 250 km south of Kolkata, around 7:30 pm today. Although more than two hundred people were injured, it is not known whether anyone died or not.</p>



<p>Odisha Chief Secretary Pradeep Jena told reporters at around 9:30 pm that the collision took place between the Coromandel Express, a local train and a freight train. Several coaches were derailed and many were damaged. About 60 ambulances and more than 15 units of the fire brigade were dispatched to the scene.</p>



<p>West Bengal Chief Minister Mamata Banerjee said that several people from Kolkata are in danger of being on this train and there is a danger of being injured. The Coromandel Express train was traveling from Kolkata&#8217;s Shalimar station to Chennai, the capital of Tamil Nadu in South India. Many people from Kolkata go to Chennai for treatment by this train.</p>



<p>Mamata Banerjee said that a team of 5 or 6 people is being sent to Odisha from West Bengal. He announced two emergency numbers for inquiries saying he was in touch with the Odisha government. These two numbers are 0091-33-22143526 and 0091-33-22535185.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/over-200-injured-in-train-accident-from-kolkata-to-chennai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 16:58:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.stetson.com/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.stetson.com/2023/06/02/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
